

I am a highly motivated individual with a passion for learning and problem-solving. I thrive on challenges and enjoy stepping outside of my comfort zone to develop new skills.

My fascination with computers and technology started at a young age and led me to study software design and development in high school, where I gained experience in basic programming, HTML, and CSS. Furthering my education at Enmore Tafe, I designed simple static websites to build my skills. These experiences provided a solid foundation for the passion for software development I still have to this day.

CONTACT



English: Native German: C1



+49 176 310 708 39



sunnyeyles@gmail.com



github.com/sunnyeyles



www.linkedin.com/in/sunny-eyles-81b259216



Bornemannstrasse 7, 13357 Berlin, Germany

SUNNY EYLES

CAREER

Software Developer Intern

April 2023 - July 2021 (Berlin, Germany)
ARUP

Building interactive web applications using React and Typescript

Barista

January 2019 - February 2021 (Berlin, Germany)

Romeo & Romeo Cafe

Cleaning and maintenance of the coffee machine and inventory management

Manager

December 2017 - July 2019 (Berlin, Germany)

Aprilkind

Hiring and training staff as well as overseeing daily operations

EDUCATION

Web and Software Development

March 2021 - March 2023 (Berlin, Germany)

Digital Career Institute GmbH

Certificate 4 Graphic Design

February 2014 - February 2015 (Sydney, Australia)

Enmore Tafe

SKILLS

- Communication & teamwork
- JavaScript, TypeScript, React
- Frontend technologies such as Bootstrap, Mantine UI, Material UI
- Backend technologies such as express and mongoose

INTERESTS

- Computers
- Fitness
- Traveling
- Reading
- InfoSec